There is a woman there; as I am talking now;
she is ready to look for her former husband.
She has lost her husband for some months now.
Her spirit is saying, 'I am going to call my husband,
I am going to look for my husband ' and say, Please, whatever happened, 'I am very sorry'.
She is there!
The woman wants to reconcile now.
I know your husband has offended you.
But you really want to reconcile.
She said, she wants to bring this man here to know God's opinion.
The woman is there.
You put a chain on your neck.
Come! She is there.
Don't worry! Please, I want to meet her.
Let her wait for me.
Prophecy Confirmation
My name is Jane Udensi.
I come from Anambra state, Nigeria.
The man of God said, there is a woman here,
and he pointed his hand in the direction where I was staying.
He said that there was a woman there - her husband left her for some months now,
and that she was ready to reconcile with her husband but there was no way.
He also mentioned that the woman put a necklace on her neck.
I confirm it to be true.
How can you confirm this prophecy to be true?
I confirm it to be true because for some months now, my husband left me.
We had been quarrelling and fighting and he left me
because of the fruit of the womb. We had had no children since we married.
It affected my marriage because there was no peace;
we fought and quarrelled all the time.
He sent me packing and married another woman
and asked me to go for another man.
There was no peace, no joy, no affection.
In the last two months, he threw my things outside and seized the others.
I didn't do anything; he beat me and threw my things outside.
I confirm the prophecy to be true.
And now that you have received this prophecy,
God Almighty has brought breakthrough, reconciliation and also healing in your life.
Yes I believe, because since the man of God called me out,
I know that my problem is over.
Amen, we thank Jesus Christ for the wonderful prophecy you have received today.
Today is your divine appointment with Jesus Christ.
And we believe that your way has been opened.
We want to encourage you, to make God's Word the standard for your life,
so that you can maintain the wonderful healing that you are about to receive
and the reconciliation, in Jesus' name.
Amen
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Jane Udensi. I come from Anambra state, Nigeria.
Last Sunday the man of God prophesied that there was a woman there
who had left her husband for more than two months now.
The woman was wearing a necklace and wanted to reconcile with her husband but he refused.
Then I came out.
He sent me away because since we got married, we have not had children and there was no affection.
He also said I had a spiritual husband that had been tormenting him in his dreams.
He said that I was an ogbanje (witch) and was causing him to be sick.
I think reasonably, we should hear from our brother.
My name is Ogochukwu Udensi. I came from Anambra state, Nigeria.
It's true that I sent my wife away because since we married, there has been no child.
There has been no affection because my wife had a spiritual husband
that had been tormenting me in my dreams.
He would carry a gun, or knife and pursue me.
He came physically?
No. In dreams, Man of God.
How? Tell us how he came in the dream!
He would carry a gun. Sometimes, he would carry a knife and I would run.
The spiritual husband resembled my wife, and pursued me with a gun.
How did you know that it was your wife that turned into a spiritual husband?
Because I could see her face.
That is why you pursued her out?
Yes. It is true, Man of God.
He said the reason why he pursued the woman out, the marriage collapsed
because he used to see this woman in the dream coming to attack him with a gun, weapon,
and he always found himself running.
In real life, did your wife use to pursue you?
No
Your wife cannot stand you in the physical. Then, why are you running in the dream?
And you know it is your wife. Why can't you wait for her?
Because she wanted to kill me.
That is why I ran.
Both of them need deliverance.
And after the deliverance, he will know that he is more of an enemy than friend to his wife.
And the wife too is more of an enemy than friend.
Do you listen to me?
I will repeat again.
You are more of an enemy than a friend to your wife. Your wife is more of an enemy than friend to you.
So who is a witch, who is a wizard now?
If the wife is a witch, he himself is a wizard.
Please tell him: If truly the wife is a witch, he himself is a wizard.
That is all. The two of them need deliverance.
Thank you.
They are husband and wife. This is a marriage from God.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.